lotusf1team.com 2011-11-17

# Team Lotus - Privacy

Team Lotus has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web Site:  
http://www.teamlotus.co.uk

1\.     COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

1.1    We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your membership information and to gather broad demographic information.

1.2    Our Customer Care feedback form requires users to give us contact information (e.g. their name and email address) so that we can respond to their comments. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.  If you contact us, we may also keep a record of that correspondence.

2\.     INFORMATION ON COOKIES

A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. We use cookies in some of our pages to store visitors' preferences and record session information. The information that we collect is then used to ensure a more personalized service level for our users. You can adjust settings on your browser so that you will be notified when you receive a cookie, giving you a choice to either refuse or accept it.

3\.     LINKS TO OTHER SITES

This site contains links to other sites. Team Lotus is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. Please also refer to Paragraph 2 of our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.teamlotus.co.uk/terms "Terms and Conditions").

4\.     SECURITY ISSUES

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We employ sophisticated technology to ensure that the sensitive information that you submit to us will be secured, safe and is password protected to prevent misuse.

5\.     WHERE WE STORE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff maybe engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. 1Malaysia Racing Team Sdn Bhd will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

6.    YOUR RIGHTS

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us at hello@teamlotus.co.uk.

7\.     ACCESS TO INFORMATION

The Data Protection Act 1998 gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

8.    DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section 1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;

  * If 1Malaysia Racing Team Sdn Bhd or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; and

  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use www.teamlotus.co.uk/terms and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of 1Malaysia Racing Team Sdn Bhd, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

9\.     CHANGES OF POLICY

Please note that we review our privacy practices from time to time, and that such practices are subject to change. We ask that our visitors periodically review this page to ensure familiarity with the most current version of our privacy statement.

10\.     QUESTIONS? / CONTACTING THE WEB SITE

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, the practices of our site, or your dealings with this Web Site, you can contact:

1Malaysia Racing Team Sdn Bhd (Company No.: 821111-V)  
Suite 3.01, Plaza Harmodal  
Jalan 13/2  
46200 Petaling Jaya  
Selangor  
Malaysia
